{
  "collection": [
    {
      "id": "01925ed0-c686-7dc8-87af-41faeb114c0f",
      "name": "Spanish",
      "flashcards": {
        "01925ed4-1d16-700c-a19d-c9d6330f8120": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-700c-a19d-c9d6330f8120",
          "front": "Nosotros asistimos a clases de cerámica",
          "back": "We attend pottery classes",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7860-9dbe-aea11cf2017a": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7860-9dbe-aea11cf2017a",
          "front": "El aire es fresco y limpio",
          "back": "The air is fresh and clean",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7563-9360-86e7ca7bdd9d": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7563-9360-86e7ca7bdd9d",
          "front": "¡Por favor!",
          "back": "Please!",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7ba3-af1a-56dda7449566": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7ba3-af1a-56dda7449566",
          "front": "¡Allá tú!",
          "back": "It's up to you!",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-76a9-89fd-0f2ffabc23a3": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-76a9-89fd-0f2ffabc23a3",
          "front": "Me duermo rápidamente",
          "back": "I fall asleep quickly",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-71dd-bef7-b74e3dc2d43a": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-71dd-bef7-b74e3dc2d43a",
          "front": "el buffet libre",
          "back": "the all-you-can-eat buffet",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7f6b-a57b-86ce7b98959c": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7f6b-a57b-86ce7b98959c",
          "front": "el café descafeinado",
          "back": "the decaffeinated coffee",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-75ff-834b-cb3b4d7d4826": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-75ff-834b-cb3b4d7d4826",
          "front": "el tren de alta velocidad",
          "back": "the high-speed train",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-720a-859c-3e4fec948209": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-720a-859c-3e4fec948209",
          "front": "¡Felices sueños!",
          "back": "Sweet dreams!",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7ccd-81d6-adaa2c0e03b1": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7ccd-81d6-adaa2c0e03b1",
          "front": "Él es un jugador de baloncesto alto",
          "back": "He is a tall basketball player",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-74c2-b77c-d993dbd81d79": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-74c2-b77c-d993dbd81d79",
          "front": "Ella es una astronauta valiente",
          "back": "She is a brave astronaut",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7934-8a52-2d9bc0272253": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7934-8a52-2d9bc0272253",
          "front": "La gallina pone huevos",
          "back": "The hen lays eggs",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7ca7-b11b-220cb358c7e7": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7ca7-b11b-220cb358c7e7",
          "front": "Estoy embarazada",
          "back": "I am pregnant",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-77a5-b400-aca22a13c52b": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-77a5-b400-aca22a13c52b",
          "front": "la propina generosa",
          "back": "the generous tip",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7d72-940d-be6e79b337d6": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7d72-940d-be6e79b337d6",
          "front": "un batido de frutas",
          "back": "a fruit smoothie",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7499-ba4a-27d766cd533a": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7499-ba4a-27d766cd533a",
          "front": "El agricultor trabaja en el campo",
          "back": "The farmer works in the field",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7d2d-b496-f58da1a9e16d": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7d2d-b496-f58da1a9e16d",
          "front": "Estar como una cabra",
          "back": "To be a bit crazy (literally: to be like a goat)",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-76b7-addd-679fe5a55711": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-76b7-addd-679fe5a55711",
          "front": "Ella está enamorada de Juan",
          "back": "She is in love with Juan",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7813-befd-51d82ef94576": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7813-befd-51d82ef94576",
          "front": "¡Basta!",
          "back": "Enough!",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7c34-98a2-be4e8a8abde8": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7c34-98a2-be4e8a8abde8",
          "front": "Él tiene hombros anchos",
          "back": "He has broad shoulders",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7ea4-96cc-e02c08bb00f0": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7ea4-96cc-e02c08bb00f0",
          "front": "Mi cabeza me duele",
          "back": "My head hurts",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7457-b889-d310d025404f": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7457-b889-d310d025404f",
          "front": "El perro ladra fuerte",
          "back": "The dog barks loudly",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7105-82e2-9f82cbc00f67": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7105-82e2-9f82cbc00f67",
          "front": "El reloj marca las doce del mediodía",
          "back": "The clock strikes twelve noon",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed4-1d16-7831-a3dc-3171d2b36798": {
          "id": "01925ed4-1d16-7831-a3dc-3171d2b36798",
          "front": "El soldado defiende el país",
          "back": "The soldier defends the country",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        }
      },
      "cardStatusMap": {
        "cardStatusMap": {
          "CardStatus.notPresented": [],
          "CardStatus.newCards": [],
          "CardStatus.oneTime": [],
          "CardStatus.twoTimes": [],
          "CardStatus.occasional": [],
          "CardStatus.errorCorrection": []
        }
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "01925ed0-c686-727e-af24-d558b13e766d",
      "name": "French",
      "flashcards": {
        "01925ed0-c685-73be-b39f-b5ec1c0dd579": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-73be-b39f-b5ec1c0dd579",
          "front": "J'ai mal à la tête",
          "back": "My head hurts",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7878-b84f-107837eaa6ee": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7878-b84f-107837eaa6ee",
          "front": "Il a les yeux bleus",
          "back": "He has blue eyes",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7c15-8c54-90bdb5ca38ba": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7c15-8c54-90bdb5ca38ba",
          "front": "Je me brosse les dents chaque jour",
          "back": "I brush my teeth every day",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7a21-af3b-7b492a178d0f": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7a21-af3b-7b492a178d0f",
          "front": "Les mains sont sales",
          "back": "The hands are dirty",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7a99-81a0-839776d5a38a": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7a99-81a0-839776d5a38a",
          "front": "Je me suis blessé le pied en jouant au football",
          "back": "I hurt my foot playing soccer",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-722a-b50f-406ba8f6e2e8": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-722a-b50f-406ba8f6e2e8",
          "front": "Les enfants se lavent le visage",
          "back": "The children wash their faces",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7353-85ac-da7f0f16a3bd": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7353-85ac-da7f0f16a3bd",
          "front": "J'ai une cicatrice sur le genou",
          "back": "I have a scar on my knee",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7756-93e6-5de24b960102": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7756-93e6-5de24b960102",
          "front": "Je me suis coupé le doigt en cuisinant",
          "back": "I cut my finger while cooking",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7229-aae9-fc45219c2178": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7229-aae9-fc45219c2178",
          "front": "Le cœur bat vite",
          "back": "The heart beats fast",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-726a-83c9-a1e59eaa8cf5": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-726a-83c9-a1e59eaa8cf5",
          "front": "Les oreilles servent à entendre",
          "back": "Ears are used for hearing",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7f27-8782-8bdbbc750547": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7f27-8782-8bdbbc750547",
          "front": "Elle a mis une bague à son doigt",
          "back": "She put a ring on her finger",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7936-934e-c394f2e01137": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7936-934e-c394f2e01137",
          "front": "J'ai besoin de reposer mon dos",
          "back": "I need to rest my back",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7c4b-8565-10e286a5cd6e": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7c4b-8565-10e286a5cd6e",
          "front": "Il a une barbe sur le menton",
          "back": "He has a beard on his chin",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-71e3-90f5-d27e7db239ed": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-71e3-90f5-d27e7db239ed",
          "front": "Mes muscles me font mal après avoir couru",
          "back": "My muscles hurt after running",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-71c7-b8e4-96dd3a8738f4": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-71c7-b8e4-96dd3a8738f4",
          "front": "Les poumons aident à respirer",
          "back": "The lungs help us breathe",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7998-9609-2d0b19f741de": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7998-9609-2d0b19f741de",
          "front": "Elle s'est peint les ongles",
          "back": "She painted her nails",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-76a3-9440-980a32df286b": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-76a3-9440-980a32df286b",
          "front": "Je me suis foulé la cheville en jouant au basket",
          "back": "I sprained my ankle playing basketball",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-77c6-9211-d0e262a378cc": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-77c6-9211-d0e262a378cc",
          "front": "Les sourcils donnent de l'expression au visage",
          "back": "Eyebrows give expression to the face",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7fc9-9fb6-ffef340b3812": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7fc9-9fb6-ffef340b3812",
          "front": "Il a de larges épaules",
          "back": "He has broad shoulders",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7784-ad87-bace1f357130": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7784-ad87-bace1f357130",
          "front": "L'estomac est vide",
          "back": "The stomach is empty",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7d87-b081-44deaed05a3f": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7d87-b081-44deaed05a3f",
          "front": "Les jambes sont fatiguées",
          "back": "The legs are tired",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7e83-8ebc-8751b8c5e130": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7e83-8ebc-8751b8c5e130",
          "front": "Le cou soutient la tête",
          "back": "The neck supports the head",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7d77-969d-3d385f5c33db": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7d77-969d-3d385f5c33db",
          "front": "Je me suis brûlé la langue avec le café chaud",
          "back": "I burned my tongue with hot coffee",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7109-a61d-0dc6012c1851": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7109-a61d-0dc6012c1851",
          "front": "Les lèvres sont sèches",
          "back": "The lips are dry",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-702c-b495-6596fedf816f": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-702c-b495-6596fedf816f",
          "front": "J'ai besoin d'étirer mes bras",
          "back": "I need to stretch my arms",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7a4e-9f59-501999cce72f": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7a4e-9f59-501999cce72f",
          "front": "Le cerveau est un organe complexe",
          "back": "The brain is a complex organ",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7066-a3dc-a6d9a1bfc98a": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7066-a3dc-a6d9a1bfc98a",
          "front": "Je me suis cogné le front contre la porte",
          "back": "I hit my forehead on the door",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7142-928f-5851b6b7e473": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7142-928f-5851b6b7e473",
          "front": "Elle a de longs cils",
          "back": "She has long eyelashes",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        },
        "01925ed0-c685-7892-9b74-37dd0356add0": {
          "id": "01925ed0-c685-7892-9b74-37dd0356add0",
          "front": "Mes genoux me font mal en montant les escaliers",
          "back": "My knees hurt when climbing stairs",
          "history": { "frontResults": [], "backResults": [] }
        }
      },
      "cardStatusMap": {
        "cardStatusMap": {
          "CardStatus.notPresented": [],
          "CardStatus.newCards": [],
          "CardStatus.oneTime": [],
          "CardStatus.twoTimes": [],
          "CardStatus.occasional": [],
          "CardStatus.errorCorrection": []
        }
      }
    }
  ]
}
